[{
    "theme": "ðŸ›« En un vuelo a EspaÃ±a",
    "langread": "en",
    "questions": [{
            "question": "How do you ask 'Where is it?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿DÃ³nde estÃ¡?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'to stop'?",
            "answers": ["parar"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'bus stop'?",
            "answers": ["la parada de autobuses"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Where is the bus stop?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿DÃ³nde estÃ¡ la parada de autobuses?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'It's on the right'?",
            "answers": ["EstÃ¡ a la derecha"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'It's on the left'?",
            "answers": ["EstÃ¡ a la izquierda"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'near'?",
            "answers": ["cerca"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'far'?",
            "answers": ["lejos"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Is it near here?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿EstÃ¡ cerca de aquÃ­?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Is it far from here?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿EstÃ¡ lejos de aquÃ­?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Is the hotel far from here?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿El hotel estÃ¡ lejos de aquÃ­?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you politely call a waiter?",
            "answers": ["Â¡Oiga, por favor!"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I want a beer'?",
            "answers": ["Quiero una cerveza"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'a glass of beer'?",
            "answers": ["una caÃ±a"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'I want a coffee with milk'?",
            "answers": ["Quiero un cafÃ© con leche"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'a coffee with a little milk'?",
            "answers": ["un cortado"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'The bill, please'?",
            "answers": ["La cuenta, por favor"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Can you bring us the bill, please?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿Nos trae la cuenta, por favor?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Bring us the bill, please'?",
            "answers": ["TrÃ¡iganos la cuenta, por favor"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'the restaurant'?",
            "answers": ["el restaurante"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'tourist office'?",
            "answers": ["la oficina de turismo"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'pharmacy'?",
            "answers": ["la farmacia"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'tobacconist shop'?",
            "answers": ["el estanco"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'a postcard'?",
            "answers": ["una tarjeta postal"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'some postcards'?",
            "answers": ["unas tarjetas postales"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'a stamp'?",
            "answers": ["un sello"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How can I help you?' (formal, singular)?",
            "answers": ["Â¿En quÃ© puedo ayudarle?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How can I help you?' (formal, plural)?",
            "answers": ["Â¿En quÃ© puedo ayudarles?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How can I serve you?' (formal, singular)?",
            "answers": ["Â¿En quÃ© puedo servirle?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'How can I serve you?' (formal, plural)?",
            "answers": ["Â¿En quÃ© puedo servirles?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Anything else?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿Algo mÃ¡s?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you ask 'Do you need anything else?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿Necesita algo mÃ¡s?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Would you like anything else?'",
            "answers": ["Â¿Quisiera algo mÃ¡s?"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Thank you'?",
            "answers": ["Gracias"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Thank you very much'?",
            "answers": ["Muchas gracias"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Thanks a lot'?",
            "answers": ["MuchÃ­simas gracias"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'You're welcome'?",
            "answers": ["De nada"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'No need to thank me'?",
            "answers": ["No hay de quÃ©"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Good morning'?",
            "answers": ["Buenos dÃ­as"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Good afternoon'?",
            "answers": ["Buenas tardes"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'Good night'?",
            "answers": ["Buenas noches"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you greet quickly in a shop?",
            "answers": ["Buenas"]
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you say 'See you next week'?",
            "answers": ["Hasta la prÃ³xima semana"]
        }
    ]
}]
